<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/"/>
  <updated>2011-11-01T17:02:35+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Israeli-made political news site]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/12/19/new-israeli-made-political-news-site.html"/>
    <updated>2007-12-19T14:37:01+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/12/19/new-israeli-made-political-news-site</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I want to inform the Zionist.com community of a new Israeli-created
political news website that I think will interest many of you news and
politics junkies. <a href="http://www.skewz.com">Skewz</a> is similar to other
&#8220;social&#8221; news sites in that you have to register as a member of the site
before submitting the stories and links that make up the site&#8217;s content.
It then departs from the norm by offering a sliding scale you can use to
filter what stories and links you are shown based on political slant,
ranging from radically left-wing to far right-wing. I, for one, find
this very useful, as I typically depend on trusted blogs and other
personal commentary sites to bring me up to speed on political issues I
may run across but have little understanding of. For example, I have
been in Israel my entire adult life, so have little understanding of the
health care debate that is such a major fixture of the US presidential
campaign. When something happens or is said regarding this issue, I
usually scan the mainstream media reports about it, and then head to the
blogs and commentary sites to learn the background info. Now, when I do
this, I prefer to be schooled by authors who share my conservative
outlook (though I don&#8217;t shy away from peeking at what the other side it
saying also). But with most social news sites that aggregate blogs and
commentary websites, I receive a deluge of results from left-leaning
writers. <a href="http://www.skewz.com">Skewz</a> allows me to eliminate that
clutter and be served results that are more in line with how I would
view the topic, if I was more knowledgeable about American health care.
The user base at Skewz is not very big yet, so the content selection is
still a bit slim. But with the presidential election just around the
corner, I think the site will grow quickly and will become a great
resource for folks like me. Check it out:
<a href="http://www.skewz.com">www.skewz.com</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[US intelligence, Iran and the Israel factor]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/12/09/us-intelligence-iran-and-the-israel-factor.html"/>
    <updated>2007-12-09T19:41:45+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/12/09/us-intelligence-iran-and-the-israel-factor</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Like many others, I was initially shocked when I read last week that US
intelligence had determined with &#8220;moderate confidence&#8221; that Iran
abandoned its quest for nuclear weapons in 2003. Hadn&#8217;t US intelligence
determined just 11 months earlier with a far greater degree of
confidence that Iran was determined, despite the potential consequences,
to develop nuclear military power? From the <a href="http://www.state.gov/s/inr/rls/79065.htm">US Annual Threat
Assessment</a> delivered on
January 11, 2007: > We assess that Tehran is determined to develop
nuclear weapons&#8211;despite its international obligations and international
pressure. But then I began to process this development in the context of
the rest of the news surrounding it. Like his father and Bill Clinton
before him, President George W. Bush is determined to carve out for
himself a positive legacy before the end of his presidency. Mr. Bush
can&#8217;t do that if his second terms ends with the entire Muslim world
hating him. And while there is little hope of convincing the Muslim
world to suddenly love America, let alone the Bush Administration, there
is no hope whatsoever of that happening if Israel strikes Iran with
tacit US approval. Israeli leaders responded to the US intelligence
report by stressing that Israeli intelligence did not concur with the
conclusions, and that Israel would still strike Iran if it felt there
was no other option. But an Israel cabinet minister <a href="http://imra.org.il/story.php3?id=37147">told <em>Time</em>
magazine</a> what everyone knows to
be true: that the US report had effectively taken the option of a
preemptive Israeli strike off the table, since Israel did not intend to
attack Iran without the green light the Olmert government believes it
needs from Washington. In addition to that, I believe, as do others I
have spoken to, that the findings of this report are part of the overall
scheme to divide the Land of Israel. Again, like his father and Bill
Clinton before him, the creation of a Palestinian Arab state would be
the jewel in the crown Bush hopes will be his legacy. Bush declared with
messianic vigor in 2004 that he would be the one to <a href="http://www.jnewswire.com/article/268">bring peace to the
Middle East</a>, and he is determined
to see that pledge through. However, Mr. Bush only has one year left to
get things done, and we are no further along in the &#8220;peace&#8221; process
today than we were 10 years ago. How in the world could this situation
possibly be brought to a head in just one year? Well, it certainly won&#8217;t
if there are other major regional concerns, like a nuclear Iran. So the
US took that concern off the table in order to focus maximum attention
on ramming through the division of the Land of Israel. If you ask me,
Bush and Rice are not to be believed when they express frustration over
the findings of the intelligence report. This is all part of the plan.
<a href="http://www.stangoodenough.com/?p=94">Stan has written a must-read analysis of this
situation</a>, explaining how the US
intelligence report is only the latest piece of evidence that in the
end, Israel will stand alone with no national friends or allies.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defend Israel - join an anti-Annapolis summit rally!]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/11/13/defend-israel-join-an-anti-annapolis-summit-rally.html"/>
    <updated>2007-11-13T11:35:47+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/11/13/defend-israel-join-an-anti-annapolis-summit-rally</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I received the following email this week from a man whose US-based
ministry has long fought to defend Israel and its biblical right to this
land. He and others like him are urgently calling for all Israel-loving
Bible believers to make their way to Washington, DC and Annapolis,
Maryland to confront the latest satanic attempt to divide this land and
thwart God&#8217;s plans. > Jerusalem is in danger. The nation of Israel is
in danger. Our families and communities are in danger. There is a battle
raging, a revolution formulating and it is not focused on the Jews
alone. What we see happening in Israel today with the people who refer
to themselves as Palestinians is merely a war by proxy aimed at
controlling God&#8217;s very throne, the place where He said His name would be
known FOREVER, Jerusalem, more precisely Mount Moriah - the Temple
Mount. > > If Islam can dominate the land of Israel and push the Jews
into the Mediterranean (which to this day is the stated goal of PLO
charter) there will be no stabilizing force to hold back the pan-Arab
takeover of the Asian and African Continents, there will be no bridle in
the mouth of the descendants of Ishmael who God Himself foretold would
be a wild ass among men. Make no mistake about it, Islam is a revolution
on a global scale. The Imams are teaching that their pseudo-god provided
his faithful followers with an abundant supply of oil to fund the spread
of Islam throughout the Earth. The oil is running out with only another
twenty years left to accomplish their deed. This, to the point of total
domination, where the infidel or unbeliever is only allowed to survive
as a slave and is heavily taxed. This can already be seen happening in
most of the Islamic countries throughout the world today. > > My point
is this - Right now the framework is being set for an unprecedented take
over of Israel&#8217;s biblical inheritance. If Islam takes control of the
land now being proposed, not only will there not be peace in the Middle
East, the stage will be set for insurrection throughout the world.
<strong>There is a unique opportunity to make a stand to help protect Israel
from Arab aggression while never leaving American soil.</strong> We can make a
difference, together, at a time when Israel is having her arm twisted by
an administration desperate to create a legacy for itself at the expense
of the Jewish people. > > We can lift our voices in opposition at the
front of the White House and at the front gate of the Annapolis Naval
Academy. Permits to assemble have been secured at both venues on the
dates of the conference in Annapolis. We need voices. We need faithful
believers who can come together and say to the mountain of political
coercion facing Israel, be removed. > > A coalition of Jewish and
Christian organizations is working together to rally support for Israel
and defend Jerusalem from Arab aggression. The dates for the rallies are
November 25 at the White House and the 26th and 27th at Annapolis. > >
Sincerely, > Ed Warmoth > Builders of Zion Executive Director >
<a href="mailto:ed@buildersofzion.org">ed@buildersofzion.org</a> >
<a href="www.buildersofzion.org">www.buildersofzion.org</a> > US Phone:
407-971-7631 These guys clearly understand that this battle is a
spiritual one at its root, and that action is needed. Many Christians,
even ones who firmly support and love Israel, believe that since
everything is ultimately in God&#8217;s hands anyway, there is no need for us
to take action. This position is wrong. If anything, the Bible teaches
us that God desires to accomplish His will through us. He has honored us
by inviting us to partner with Him, and we should not miss that
opportunity. If you are able, make every effort to be one of those
physically and publicly standing for Israel when later this month the
nations of the world again come against her to try and wrest control of
the most important and strategic parts of this land.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sign the Declaration of Solidarity with Israel]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/22/sign-the-declaration-of-solidarity-with-israel.html"/>
    <updated>2007-10-22T14:37:28+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/22/sign-the-declaration-of-solidarity-with-israel</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I was recently made aware of an online petition currently making the
rounds that I would encourage everyone who opposes the surrender of even
one inch of the biblical Land of Israel to the Muslim Arab world to
sign. The petition comes in two forms: a motion of no-confidence in the
Israeli government for Israeli citizens to sign, and a Declaration of
Solidarity for non-Israelis to sign. Both, say the organizers of the
petition, will act to give courage to Israeli lawmakers to stand up to
their out-of-control government that seems bent on capitulating to the
enemies of the Jewish state. The petition can be found here:
<a href="http://www.strongisrael.org">www.strongisrael.org</a> While this petition
alone is unlikely to sway Olmert, who insists he is under no obligation
to seek even the Knesset&#8217;s approval in negotiating away Israel&#8217;s
birthright, it never hurts to let Israelis know just how many people out
there stand firmly with their right to possess all of their God-given
heritage. Also, the website linked above has a wealth of information
regarding the true intentions of the &#8220;moderate&#8221; Palestinian forces
Olmert will find himself across the table from in Annapolis next month.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Right, wrong and the Israeli-Arab peace process]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/22/right-wrong-and-the-israeli-arab-peace-process.html"/>
    <updated>2007-10-22T14:20:02+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/22/right-wrong-and-the-israeli-arab-peace-process</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Former Israeli Knesset Member and Minister of Justice Tommy Lapid argued
persuasively, but erroneously in a recent <em>Jerusalem Post</em> op-ed that
both Prime Minister Ehud Olmert and opposition leader Binyamin Netanyahu
are right in their contrasting approaches to the peace process. Olmert
knows that he must at least try to engage the Arabs in dialogue, and
wean his nation off the belief that all the dreams, hopes and prayers of
generations of Jews can be fulfilled in the midst of the present
conflict, wrote Lapid. But that doesn&#8217;t mean Netanyahu is wrong to warn
of the dangers inherent in Olmert&#8217;s course of action. If the weak and
seemingly incapable regime of Palestinian Authority Chairman Mahmoud
Abbas, with whom Olmert is negotiating the surrender of the West Bank,
is again defeated by Hamas as it was in Gaza, &#8220;not only Tel Aviv&#8230;will
share the fate of Sderot, but so will Ben-Gurion Airport, cutting off
Israel&#8217;s ties with the world,&#8221; Lapid conceded. Israel, Lapid concluded,
simply has no choice but to soldier on along this path of disparate
political approaches, as &#8220;there is no practical solution to the conflict
in sight. &#8230;Some situations have no solutions. And for the time being,
life goes on.&#8221; That conclusion sounds reasonable, if not bleak, on the
surface, but falls apart if we dig a little deeper. Lapid fails to
entertain the option of one side in this equation - either the right led
by Netanyahu, or the left led by Olmert - waking up to reality and
backing the other&#8217;s position. While it is unlikely to happen, examining
the consequences of such an occurrence shows precisely why both sides
are not right. If, as Lapid accepts, Netanyahu is correct in his current
assertion that true and lasting peace cannot be made with the Abbas-led
Palestinian Authority regardless of how much Israel gives, then for
Netanyahu and the bulk of his followers to adopt Olmert&#8217;s position would
lead to catastrophe. However, for Olmert and the left to adopt
Netanyahu&#8217;s position would signal a seismic shift in an increasingly
pointless diplomatic process that has produced plenty of photo
opportunities and little peace since its inception more than a decade
ago. Lapid suggests that the right&#8217;s alternative to Olmert actively
pursuing doomed land-for-peace negotiations with the Palestinians is to
create a diplomatic vacuum, to more or less ignore the issue all
together. Lapid is right that such a scenario would invite &#8220;pressures
that we would find it impossible to withstand.&#8221; But Lapid is wrong in
thinking that the right&#8217;s substitute for offering strategic concessions
to an intractable foe is diplomatic idleness. Netanyahu has long
insisted that it is his desire to find a truly workable solution to the
conflict, and one of the right&#8217;s more active members in this arena,
National Union Party chief Rabbi Benny Elon, just launched a thoroughly
detailed alternative peace plan of his own. The ideas being put forth by
the right might not result in bilateral peace, but for the nation at
large to embrace them would signal to the world that Jewish history and
Israeli security are no longer being offered as sacrifices on the alter
of a false peace. And that would restore national pride, dignity and a
willingness to fight for Israel&#8217;s rights to levels that have not been
seen since the early years of the Jewish state&#8217;s rebirth. Lapid and
others on the left see the right&#8217;s alternatives as little more than hot
air because Israelis have been trained over the past decade by an
idealistic peace movement to view such proposals as wildly unrealistic.
How many times over the past three years alone have we heard Olmert and
Ariel Sharon before him lament that holding on to the full Zionist dream
has become an unfeasible and even irrational notion? The truth is that
the concept of land-for-peace has become unrealistic, just as the
insistence that this is a purely political and nationalistic struggle
that has nothing to do with religion has become untenable. The lesson
Israelis should have learned over the past decade as a result of
continued Palestinian intransigence and Hamas gains is that concessions
and goodwill are clearly not going to lead to peace, and offering them
will only embolden an enemy that has no intention of relinquishing its
quest to ultimately regain all that was once under Islam&#8217;s dominion.
Lapid is right in seeing no practical solution to the conflict. He is
wrong in thinking that Israel has no choice but to go along with this
moribund process anyway, to the detriment of its own cause and the well
being of its citizens.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will America buy the latest Palestinian lies?]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/22/will-america-buy-the-latest-palestinian-lies.html"/>
    <updated>2007-10-22T11:49:42+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/22/will-america-buy-the-latest-palestinian-lies</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Israel&#8217;s wayward leadership is trying to cleverly minimize the damage
done to their nation at the upcoming US-hosted peace summit in Annapolis
by insisting that the faltering Middle East peace process remain tied to
the Washington-backed Road Map peace plan. The reason for hoisting the
Road Map as the standard for peacemaking is that the plan is a
performance-based one that if accurately followed would require the
Palestinians to finally provide Israel with the peace, security and rest
from aggression it has so long sought. Failure on the Palestinians&#8217; part
to do so is supposed to negate Israel&#8217;s obligation to turn over any
additional territory. So what do the Palestinians do? They naturally
launch a campaign to convince the Bush Administration and other world
leaders that they have <a href="http://www.israelnationalnews.com/News/Flash.aspx/135025">already fulfilled all their obligations under
the first phase of the Road
Map</a>, and are
now awaiting Israel&#8217;s reciprocation. It is a laughable claim, but
unfortunately for Israel it is probably enough to outflank Jerusalem&#8217;s
diplomatic position since Washington and the world have never been much
for fact-checking when it comes to Palestinian assertions, regardless of
how wild they may be. The very fact that we are talking about a people
group known as the &#8220;Palestinians&#8221; at all is evidence of that. So what
does Phase One of the US-authored Road Map demand of the Palestinians?
To put it simply, the Road Map demands that the Palestinian leadership
explicitly recognize Israel&#8217;s right to exist in this region, renounce
and combat the use of terrorist violence against Israelis, and put an
end to incitement against Israel and the Jews in the Palestinian media
and school system. I doubt it is necessary to expound upon how these
commitments have been anything but fulfilled by the Palestinian
Authority. Suffice it to say that Palestinian leaders (when speaking in
Arabic) continue to employ language that provides hope of one day
eradicating Jewish sovereignty, successful and attempted attacks on
Israelis continue unabated, and Palestinian children are still being
taught by their teachers and favorite television characters to loathe
the Jews and seek &#8220;martyrdom&#8221; while fighting them. Tens minutes on the
Internet making elementary use of Google is sufficient to punch numerous
holes in the latest Palestinian diplomatic position. The question is
whether Washington will champion truth and justice, or if it will put
perceived American interests in the Middle East ahead of Israeli lives
and again sell the Jewish state down the river.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jerusalem the stumbling block]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/10/jerusalem-the-stumbling-block.html"/>
    <updated>2007-10-10T17:44:40+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/10/jerusalem-the-stumbling-block</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The international community will bring the Israelis and Arabs together
in Annapolis, Maryland next month to again try to solve the Middle East
conflict according to its own wisdom and humanist agenda. It will fail,
as it has every other time, and it looks like Jerusalem will once again
be the stumbling block that prevents any real progress down the false
path to peace. Israel&#8217;s deputy prime minister is openly admitting that
the <a href="http://www.ynetnews.com/articles/0,7340,L-3457214,00.html">division of Jerusalem will be on the
table</a> at the
upcoming summit. Even Prime Minister Ehud Olmert, once the mayor of what
he insisted would always be the &#8220;eternal, undivided capital&#8221; of the
Jewish people, seems to be backing that position. But rather than jump
on the offer and then work to get more later, the Palestinians are
<a href="http://www.jpost.com/servlet/Satellite?cid=1191257255317&amp;pagename=JPost%2FJPArticle%2FPrinter">hardening their
positions</a>
before negotiations have even began, making demands that would
necessitate uprooting well over 100,000 Jews from densely populated
neighborhoods - a concession the Palestinians know full well Olmert is
simply in no position to make. Why would they do this? Why would the
Palestinians make demands they know it is impossible for Olmert to meet,
instead of taking everything he is offering now and then demanding more
later? The Palestinians and the backers of their cause claim that offers
that do not meet 100% of their demands cannot be accepted because doing
so would prevent them from ever reaching their full goals. I would like
to note that in 1993, Yasser Arafat and his PLO ostensibly renounced the
use of terrorist violence against Israel and recognized the right of the
Jewish state to exist. That, however, clearly did not stop Arafat and
his Palestinians from employing terrorist violence against Israel and
seeking Jewish state&#8217;s ultimate demographic demise through a
&#8220;Palestinian right of return.&#8221; So why now would accepting most of
eastern Jerusalem prevent the Palestinians from continuing their
&#8220;struggle&#8221; to ultimately wrest control of all Jerusalem from the Jews?
Arafat also seemed to be stricken by this lack of logic when in 2000 he
turned down Ehud Barak&#8217;s offer of about 95 percent of Judea and Samaria,
including the eastern half of Jerusalem. This was the same Arafat who
knew in 1993 that he could sign deals with Israel and then not live up
to his side of the bargain, while retaining the support of the world for
future concessions. Something or someone muddled Arafat&#8217;s thinking in
2000, just as Abbas&#8217; is being muddled now. To me, it is clear that the
Lord is hardening the hearts of Israel&#8217;s enemies to prevent the world
and Israel&#8217;s own delusional leaders from going too far down this path of
destruction. That should come as no surprise to those who read and
believe the Bible. Zechariah 12 states that in these days Jerusalem will
be made a stumbling block, an immovable stone to all the nations that
try to move it, a hindrance to their plans. Expect the Annapolis summit
to fail (even if the leaders make some kind of &#8220;feel good&#8221; statement at
its closing), and expect Jerusalem to be the reason. Other good takes on
the planned division of Jerusalem: <a href="http://muqata.blogspot.com/2007/10/jerusalem-who-is-real-mother.html">Jameel over at the
Muqata</a>
notes that in the Bible, the mother who was willing to divide the baby
she claimed as hers was revealed by Solomon to not be the true mother.
<a href="http://elderofziyon.blogspot.com/2007/10/pa-willingly-cedes-control-of-jerusalem.html">The Elder of
Zion</a>
points to an Arab report that the Palestinians are willing to put
Jerusalem under Jordanian sovereignty - kind of a &#8220;if we can&#8217;t have it,
then neither can the Jews&#8221; move. However, if the Palestinians are so
ready to let the Jordanians come in, is Jerusalem really as important to
them as they claim?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pray for the Christians of Gaza]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/08/pray-for-the-christians-of-gaza.html"/>
    <updated>2007-10-08T11:57:13+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/08/pray-for-the-christians-of-gaza</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A young and by all account passionate Christian man was stabbed to death
in the Gaza Strip this past weekend in an incident that should highlight
precisely the kind of &#8220;free&#8221; and &#8220;tolerant&#8221; society the Bush
Administration and the international community are trying to create by
pushing for the establishment of a Palestinian Arab state. The young man
in question, 31-year-old Rami Ayyad, was the director of Gaza&#8217;s only
major Christian bookstore, and had been <a href="http://www.jpost.com/servlet/Satellite?cid=1191257240876&amp;pagename=JPost%2FJPArticle%2FPrinter">repeatedly threatened by local
Muslim elements for his sharing of the
Gospel</a>.
It would seem he was not intimidated by those threats, and continued to
share the love and message of the Lord. He paid for his faith and
faithfulness with his life. Ayyad was married with two small children
and a third on the way. Regurgitating the propaganda of the Palestinian
Authority and Hamas, the international media maintains that relations
between Christians and Muslims in Gaza are generally good. The reality
is that attacks and acts of intimidation have been increasing for years,
and that Christians there are merely tolerated, and that only when they
submit to dhimmi status. The most at risk are those who, like Ayyad,
share the Gospel with their Muslim neighbors, and those who accept that
message and open their hearts to the Lord (they are locally referred to
as MBBs - Muslim Background Believers, because they live in fear of
shedding the title &#8220;Muslim&#8221;). It is sickening to me that the world is
always at the ready to jump on Israel over any and every alleged
infringement of freedom of religion, but completely ignores the plight
of Palestinian Christians persecuted by their Muslim overlords. What
frustrates me even more are those American Christian organizations and
churches that actively bolster the claim that it is Israel that
oppresses these Christians. Israel did not kill Ayyad. Israel did not
bomb Ayyad&#8217;s bookstore or the Gaza Bible Society that runs it. Israel
does not send threatening letters to Arab Christians who dare to share
the love of Jesus with their Muslim neighbors. It is time to stop
misappropriating blame and time to start supporting brave souls like
Ayyad who put everything on the line, literally, to bring the truth
where it is most dangerous to do so.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abbas supports terrorism]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/07/abbas-supports-terrorism.html"/>
    <updated>2007-10-07T13:54:52+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/07/abbas-supports-terrorism</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Those who read this blog are fully aware that the Palestinian Authority
of Mahmoud Abbas is a supporter and facilitator of Muslim terrorism, but
it never hurts to remind everyone else of that fact and introduce new
evidence as to why this man and his government should not be sitting
across the negotiating table from our own leaders. Last week, a
prominent female Palestinian figure and lawmaker <a href="http://www.israelnationalnews.com/News/News.aspx/123830">issued a very public
&#8220;thank you&#8221; to
Abbas</a> after
his government resumed direct financial aid to terrorists jailed or
wounded by Israeli security forces and to the families of terrorists who
died while attacking Jews. Did you get that? Abbas is handing out money
to terrorists and their families who are adversely affected by engaging
in terrorist violence against Israeli Jews. How exactly is that
discouraging terrorism? How does that make Abbas a true peace partner?
Now, this kind of behavior from the Palestinian leadership is pretty
much par for the course. What is maddening is to listen to Israeli Prime
Minister Ehud Olmert insist that <a href="http://www.jpost.com/servlet/Satellite?cid=1189411453780&amp;pagename=JPost%2FJPArticle%2FPrinter">Abbas is a man of
peace</a>
and to US President George W. Bush claim that <a href="http://www.zoa.org/2007/09/zoa_criticizes_43.htm">the Palestinian leader is
combatting anti-Israel
terrorism</a>. Could
these guys have their heads any deeper in the sand? Didn&#8217;t the Bush
Administration make a big deal just a few years ago about Saddam Hussein
distributing financial compensation to the families of Palestinian
suicide bombers? How are Abbas&#8217; actions any different? Following the
September 11, 2001 attacks on the US, Bush insisted that leaders and
nations around the globe are either with us or with the terrorists. What
he forgot to mention was that the apparent exception to that rule are
the Palestinians, who continue to be permitted to openly keep one foot
in the terrorists&#8217; camp and the other in the White House.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worship at the Temple Mount]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/03/worship-at-the-temple-mount.html"/>
    <updated>2007-10-03T16:24:08+03:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/03/worship-at-the-temple-mount</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I joined the International Christian Zionist Center (ICZC) Feast of
Tabernacles celebration again today as the group visited and held a
worship service on the ancient steps of the Temple Mount. It was a
beautiful and inspiring experience that most everyone there agreed had
spiritually opened the gates for increased Christian efforts to bring
about the rebuilding of the temple in Jerusalem. Part of those efforts
will be - God willing - the annual presence of God-fearing,
Israel-loving Christians proclaiming the Lord&#8217;s truth regarding Israel
and the coming of her king and messiah from this very location. The spot
where the service was held will be known to any who have visited Israel.
It is on the ancient unearthed steps that extend from the southern end
of the Temple Mount, just under the Al Aqsa Mosque - the site Muslims
claim as Islam&#8217;s third holiest. The ICZC event experienced tremendous
growth this year that can only be attributed to the Lord&#8217;s blessing and
favor. If that percentage of growth continues next year, these ancient
steps will be the only other place in Jerusalem other than the Jerusalem
Convention Center (which the Christian Embassy already uses) that can
accommodate such a gathering. Pray the Lord will give the ICZC favor to
secure the ancient Temple Mount steps for every evening of next year&#8217;s
feast. Needless to say, the Muslims inside Al Aqsa were not too happy
about 500 Christians proclaiming God&#8217;s Word, praying for Israel&#8217;s full
restoration, and worshiping the God of Abraham, Isaac and Jacob just
outside their windows. Throughout the service Muslims inside the mosque
could be seen watching us from the windows, and even taking pictures of
the group. Pray that the spirit of Islam will quickly be broken over
this holy hill, and that as many as possible of those Muslims whose
hearts and minds are held captive by Allah will be freed. It really
seems that we are nearing something big. Events like this reinforce the
feeling that we are very rapidly nearing the end of all things
prophesied in His Word. And we will be even closer next year when
thousands of Christians who love His Name and His Word gather nightly at
the steps of His ancient and future temple to worship and do warfare
against the spirit of Islam.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arabs persecuted for loving Israel]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/02/arabs-persecuted-for-loving-israel.html"/>
    <updated>2007-10-02T16:56:22+03:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/10/02/arabs-persecuted-for-loving-israel</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As a further follow-up to my earlier post regarding a <a href="http://www.zionist.com/2007/09/30/arabs-loving-israelis">lovely Arab woman
from northern Israel who loves Israel and the God of Israel with all her
heart</a>, I want
to provide an example of how such servants of the Lord are being
persecuted by their own people. This same woman who just days before
embraced and was embraced by an Israeli Jewish woman from the
rocket-battered town of Sderot was on Monday the target of Israeli-Arab
Muslim aggression in Tel Aviv. As the <a href="http://www.israelmybeloved.com">International Christian Zionist
Center</a> Feast of Tabernacles group
gathered outside Israeli army headquarters in Tel Aviv, we all noticed
the conspicuous presence of an unhappy looking Arab woman in full Muslim
attire. She seemed to be zoning in on the Christian Arab woman with us,
who promptly notified the hovering Israeli security agents (imagine that
- an Arab requesting that Israeli security come investigate another
Arab). After being questioned by a security agent, the Muslim woman made
a beeline for the Christian lady and verbally assaulted her. Refusing to
address her in Arabic, the Muslim accused the Christian of &#8220;being a Jew&#8221;
due to her support of Israel and said she should be ashamed. She then
threatened that &#8220;we know who you are, and we will lay our hands on you.&#8221;
The Christian lady later told us that such confrontations are not
uncommon, and that there are Muslim groups that keep tabs on Arabs like
her to harass and even harm any that dare show love and support for
Israel. That caused me to think about the tremendous amount of courage
demonstrated by Arabs like this amazing woman traveling with us. Sure,
we are putting ourselves in a relative amount of danger by living in
Israel and openly siding with the Jewish state. But the threat to us as
foreign Christians does not even come close to that faced by Middle East
Arabs who throw in their lot with Israel. This particular woman could
very easily keep her mouth shut and remain at home, quietly loving
Israel in her heart, while avoiding the very real and deadly threat
posed to her and her family. But she is a true believer, a true servant
of the Lord, and she knows that she has no choice but to serve the Lord
openly and declare His truth regarding this nation&#8230; even at the cost
of her own life. Pray for this woman, for her family and for the others
like her who love the Lord and the &#8220;apple of His eye&#8221; more than their
own lives.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to touch Israelis]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/30/how-to-touch-israelis.html"/>
    <updated>2007-09-30T15:00:00+03:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/30/how-to-touch-israelis</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I want to add to my previous post regarding the <a href="http://www.zionist.com/2007/09/30/arabs-loving-israelis">beautiful love I
witnessed last week between an Israeli Arab mother and an Israeli Jewish
mother</a> in the
battered town of Sderot by noting the lessons I learned at that event
about touching the hearts of Israelis. I am a fairly reserved, though
straight-forward person, so I am not always comfortable in the presence
of dramatic Christian expressions of faith. I will qualify that by
noting that I am not critical of such displays - if God found favor with
David wildly dancing in his underwear in the presence of His ark, then
clearly there is nothing wrong with such behavior. Anyway, since I am
personally perhaps a little too bashful to act out in such a way myself,
I always feared that the Israelis we were visiting during these Feast of
Tabernacles outings were viewing the group as a bunch of
mentally-disturbed nut-jobs. I always feared that instead of providing
comfort, the brightly colored biblical-style clothing, the waving
banners and the chorus of shofars were instead eliciting internal
chuckles of disdain. While a handful of Israelis may indeed view the
Feast groups in such a way, I discovered in Sderot that most, especially
in locations where Israelis are hurting most, are touched to the core by
this bizarre-looking and unfamiliar outpouring of love. As the group
marched down the streets of Sderot, rather than being put off by the
costumes, flags and shofars, Israeli pedestrians were clapping, mothers
were coming out of their homes weeping and motorists blocked by our
procession were honking and cheering. Last Friday I witnessed hundreds
of Israelis being deeply touched, being comforted by hundreds of
Christians that most would write off as “freaks.” (Sadly, I have heard
even fellow believers here in Jerusalem refer to the participants in
this event in such derogatory terms.) So, while donating money to causes
in Israel or saying prayers for the Jewish state are all well and good,
if you want to really, directly touch the hearts of Israelis where they
are, then you need to get to Israel and join these “freaks” as they
bring the love of our Lord to a hurting and thirsty nation. For more
information on the annual Christian Zionist Feast of Tabernacles
celebration and the International Christian Zionist Center, visit
<a href="http://www.israelmybeloved.com">Israel My Beloved</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arabs loving Israelis]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/30/arabs-loving-israelis.html"/>
    <updated>2007-09-30T14:39:13+03:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/30/arabs-loving-israelis</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I participated in Friday&#8217;s visit to the rocket-battered town of Sderot
by some 500 participants in the International Christian Zionist Center&#8217;s
Feast of Tabernacles celebration. While the group&#8217;s march through the
town and its outpouring of love was beautiful to see, one scene in
particular brought tears to my eyes. As we arrived and the group was
lining up, an Israeli-Arab lady who had come with us went to sit at the
side in an attempt to escape the sun. This lovely Christian woman
suddenly noticed that a local Israeli woman had walked up next to her to
observe the spectacle of so many colorfully-attired Christians forming
up just outside her home. She turned to the Israeli woman and said: >
We have come to stand with you. We love you. I think about what you are
going through and I cannot sleep. Those words, coming from an Arab to an
Israeli Jew, are amazing enough. I then stood nearby and watched and
listened while these two women, these two mothers, one an Arab and the
other an Israeli Jew, held each other and cried. The Christian woman
knew exactly what the Sderot mother was going through, for just one year
earlier her own home was seriously damaged and her own children&#8217;s lives
endangered by Hizballah missiles from Lebanon. This is the kind of love
and coexistence that could exist between all Israelis and their Arab
countrymen and neighbors, if only the Arabs could be brought to the Lord
and freed from Islam and the lie that is the “Palestinian cause.” This
amazing Arab woman is living proof that her people can be staunch
Israel-loving Christian Zionists, sending their own children to fight in
defense of the Jewish state and proudly referring to themselves as
“Israelis.”</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Columbia was wrong to give Ahamdinejad a platform]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/25/why-columbia-was-wrong-to-give-ahamdinejad-a-platform.html"/>
    <updated>2007-09-25T15:44:58+03:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/25/why-columbia-was-wrong-to-give-ahamdinejad-a-platform</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Much is being made of Columbia University&#8217;s decision to let Iranian
President Mahmoud Ahmadinejad address its student body in the name of
free speech and critical dialogue. Proponents of the decision insist
that the event provided an opportunity to publicly confront the Iranian
regime&#8217;s repression of basic freedoms, denial of the Holocaust and
refusal to accept Israel&#8217;s right to exist in a public forum for all the
world to see. According to this naive thinking, the exchange at Columbia
should have served to expose the fallacy of Ahmadinejad&#8217;s positions,
thereby undercutting his support base and encouraging opposition to his
policies at home. However, it is a near certainty that the portions of
Monday&#8217;s event in which Ahmadinejad was scorned for his views or was
booed and heckled by the audience will never air in Iran. Instead,
Iranian state-controlled television will broadcast those parts of the
event in which their president was loudly applauded by the liberals in
the audience. Those scenes and the very fact that Ahmadinejad was
invited to speak at one of America&#8217;s most prominent universities are
going to provide him with a tremendous amount of prestige and legitimacy
in Iran and the Middle East, and will instead undercut his detractors.
Supporters of having the Tyrant of Tehran at Columbia also say that
American university students must be exposed to the different ideologies
and concepts that are out there, and should not hinder free speech and
the exchange of ideas, regardless of how offensive they may be to our
own sensitivities. Tellingly, Columbia regularly denies the right of
political conservatives to ascend the same platform. As an example of
the depth of Columbia&#8217;s hypocrisy, consider that at Monday&#8217;s event
Ahmadinejad insisted there are no homosexuals in Iran, which is another
way of saying he and his nation&#8217;s religious overlords will not allow
homosexuality in Iran. This position was known beforehand, yet
Ahmadinejad was invited to speak anyway, while recruiters with the US
military&#8217;s ROTC training program are barred from the campus because of
the military&#8217;s “don&#8217;t ask, don&#8217;t tell” policy regarding homosexuality.
The worst part about letting Ahmadinejad speak at Columbia University,
however, was that it lent a certain degree of legitimacy to not only the
man, but also to his venomous views. Even if no one at Columbia agreed
with Ahmadinejad regarding his revisionist view of the Nazi Holocaust
and his desire to see Israel destroyed (not to mention his regime&#8217;s
repressive practices at home) allowing him to engage the student body
and the American people at large in dialogue essentially announced that
we consider these topics to be open for discussion. It has been rightly
noted that Columbia is not alone among major American universities in
behaving thus. The combination of naivety and hypocrisy that plagues
Columbia University is increasingly prevalent throughout America
academia, and is like a Trojan Horse opening the doors to our most
dedicated enemies.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel's government aiding Temple Mount desecration]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/23/israels-government-aiding-temple-mount-desecration.html"/>
    <updated>2007-09-23T14:35:35+03:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/23/israels-government-aiding-temple-mount-desecration</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Amazingly, after Jews around the world dreamt and prayed for 2,000 years
about returning to Zion and even rebuilding their temple to the
Almighty, an Israeli government is today actively shielding the Muslim
powers that are trying to erase any Jewish connection to Jerusalem&#8217;s
Temple Mount. This past Friday, Israel&#8217;s High Court heard the response
of Prime Minister Ehud Olmert&#8217;s government to an earlier petition by
leading archeologists to have the authorities halt the destructive
excavations and renovations being carried out without supervision by the
Muslim Trust (Waqf) that oversees the Temple Mount. To the shock and
dismay of the archeologists, the judge <a href="http://imra.org.il/story.php3?id=36126">ordered them out of the
courtroom</a> so that he could be
presented with “secret evidence” by Olmert&#8217;s government “proving” that
the Muslims had caused no damage to any Jewish antiquities. Why would
these archeologists be ordered out of the courtroom unless the
government either didn&#8217;t really have any evidence or the evidence they
did have didn&#8217;t really prove anything? What seems most likely to me is
that the petitioners were ordered out so that the Olmert government
could explain to the judge without any interruptions or objections why
Israel needs to just keep its mouth shut and allow its enemies to
destroy all remains of a historical Jewish connection to the Temple
Mount so as not to disrupt “peace” efforts. Earlier this month, Israeli
television showed footage of the Muslim excavations atop the Temple
Mount. In the footage, a deep and long gash can be seen in the floor of
the compound, revealing at least one ornate ancient wall that experts
say is likely the first piece of the Second Temple to be revealed in
centuries. The wall was smashed during the dig. It is no secret that the
Muslims want to deny any Jewish connection to this most holy place. They
say as much all the time. What is shocking is that a Jewish Israeli
government is going out of its way to shield the Muslims in this
despicable act of rewriting history. A couple weeks ago, the Temple
Institute in Jerusalem called on all Bible-believing Christians to <a href="http://www.zionist.com/2007/09/06/christians-called-to-help-save-the-temple">rise
up and aid their Jewish brothers in defending the Temple Mount against
the plans of
Allah</a>.
I think it is time we answer that call, since the needed help is clearly
not going to come from Israel&#8217;s own authorities.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palestinian strategy revealed]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/23/palestinian-strategy-revealed.html"/>
    <updated>2007-09-23T12:11:29+03:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/23/palestinian-strategy-revealed</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It is no secret to those with their eyes open that even the so-called
“moderate” Palestinians belonging to Mahmoud Abbas&#8217; Fatah movement are
neck-deep in the blood of Israeli Jews and see violence as a useful and
legitimate tool in obtaining its goals. For those still on the fence on
this issue, Fatah commanders themselves are now admitting that their
group employs a strategy of sowing with the gun and reaping with
politics. Earlier this summer, Israeli Prime Minister Ehud Olmert
decided to grant amnesty to 178 Fatah terrorists as a gesture of
goodwill toward Abbas and in an effort to bolster his fragile regime,
which had recently suffered a stunning military defeat at the hand of
Hamas in Gaza. Israeli and foreign media outlets portrayed the Fatah
members participating in the move as almost repenting of their past
violence and converting to the path of dialogue. The truth, however, is
that these groups - even the “moderate” Fatah and their supporters among
the general public - believe terrorist violence against Israeli Jews is
a necessary component of their overall negotiation strategy. The
Bethlehem-based Ma&#8217;an news agency recently interviewed Abu Jabal, a
local field commander of Fatah&#8217;s Al Aqsa Brigades “military wing” in the
Samarian town of Nablus (biblical Shechem). Abu Jabal, who was among
those granted amnesty, had this to say of the <a href="http://www.maannews.net/en/index.php?opr=ShowDetails&amp;ID=25171">relationship between
Palestinian violence and
negotiations</a>:
> We have a saying in Fatah: With the gun we plant and with the
politics we harvest. A colleague, Abu Skandar, jumped in on the
interview to point out that the Fatah men did not intend to abide by the
documents they signed renouncing the use of violence against Israelis
forever. > We want to give politicians an opportunity, [but] we have
not absolutely abandoned fighting. Abu Jabal also stressed that he and
his men did not agree to the amnesty deal because they suddenly feel
remorse for attacking Jewish men, women and children, but rather because
doing so presently serves Palestinian interests: > We agreed to this
because it benefits the Palestinian people. This is “moderate” Islam,
this is the behavior of the most moderate Palestinians. It is a mistake
to see news reports of “moderate” Palestinian leaders and assume that
their moderation and behavior mirrors that of moderate folks in the
West. Our leaders in the West, however, are going to great lengths to
ignore that discrepancy. They are putting their own short-term political
interests first by pretending that people like Abbas and Abu Jabal hold
views equal to our own when it comes to terrorist activity. These
leaders refuse to acknowledge Arab admissions of remaining committed to
terrorist violence because doing so would pull the rug out from under
their own political agendas.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delusional Jimmy Carter certain Iran will never attack Israel]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/20/delusional-jimmy-carter-certain-iran-will-never-attack-israel.html"/>
    <updated>2007-09-20T16:03:20+03:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/20/delusional-jimmy-carter-certain-iran-will-never-attack-israel</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Jimmy Carter this week continued his rise as the new king of the
delusional leftists who insist Israel and the US have no real enemies
besides those they themselves provoke to hostile action. In an address
at Emory University, Carter stated adamantly that it was “almost
inconceivable” that Iran would actually attack Israel, and insisted that
the Islamic Republic does not pose any real threat to either the Jewish
state or the US. <a href="http://www.israelnationalnews.com/News/Flash.aspx/133509">Said
Carter</a>: >
Iran is quite distant from Israel. Uh, ever heard of ballistic missiles?
> I think it would be almost inconceivable that Iran would commit
suicide by launching one or two missiles of any kind against the nation
of Israel. Ok, so he has heard of ballistic missiles, but apparently
missed the memo that Iran has <a href="http://www.jpost.com/servlet/Satellite?cid=1189411419433&amp;pagename=JPost%2FJPArticle%2FPrinter">600 of them pointed at
Israel</a>,
not just two. Unbelievably, this is the same Jimmy Carter who was
president during the Islamic Revolution and the seizing of the US
Embassy in Tehran. And he somehow now finds it impossible to believe
that the same kind of Islamic madmen who perpetrated those crimes would
ever launch an attack on the Islamic world&#8217;s most hated enemy. This is
exactly the kind of delusional wishful thinking that resulted in
British-led Western Europe keeping its eyes tightly closed until
Hitler&#8217;s Germany had actually launched its conquest of the continent.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palestinians celebrate 9/11 attacks on US]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/19/palestinians-celebrate-911-attacks-on-us.html"/>
    <updated>2007-09-19T18:45:18+03:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/19/palestinians-celebrate-911-attacks-on-us</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>While the Bush Administration pours millions of US taxpayers&#8217; dollars
into the Palestinian Authority in a vain hope that that regime will ever
build and govern a viable state-like entity, the Palestinian Authority
is busy celebrating the victories of America&#8217;s enemies. For those
Americans who believe the Palestinian Authority of Mahmoud Abbas is
either moderate or pro-American, take a look at this cartoon that
featured prominently last week in a newspaper fully controlled by Abbas&#8217;
office:
<img src="http://www.zionist.com/wp-content/uploads/2007/09/binladenvictoryoverwtc-alhayat-12-9-2007.JPG" alt="Palestinian political cartoon celebrating Al Qaeda attack on
US" />
\
 The same newspaper has carried similar illustrations ever since Al
Qaeda killers downed the Twin Towers in New York City on September 11,
2001. That shouldn&#8217;t come as too much of a surprise, considering that
the Palestinians erupted in mass street celebrations as the Twin Towers
were burning and falling on top of thousands of Americans that fateful
day. I remember watching television footage of Arabs just a few miles
from me in eastern Jerusalem handing out candy and howling with joy over
the fact that Osama bin Laden had slaughtered so many infidels. And that
feeling of camaraderie with America&#8217;s enemies has clearly not waned. As
recently as 2005, a public opinion poll showed that <a href="http://www.worldnetdaily.com/news/article.asp?ARTICLE_ID=57696">a firm 65 percent
of Palestinian Arabs still supported Al Qaeda&#8217;s assault on the United
States</a>.
That the Palestinian public proudly sees itself as an enemy of the US
can be traced to its leadership, which continues to use all that US and
European money to <a href="http://www.zionist.com/2007/08/30/someone-stop-the-abuse-of-palestinian-children">educate young Palestinians to hate not only
Israel</a>,
but the entire Judeo-Christian West. Of course, that behavior can be
traced back to Islam, which teaches all Arab Muslims, both the leaders
and the general public, that all non-Muslim entities must ultimately be
warred against and conquered. Should America really be spending its
money in a way that helps forward such a message? Some will argue that
cutting off the aid will wrongfully harm the Palestinian public for the
mistakes of their leaders. But if the money being given to the
Palestinians for education and other social assistance efforts is being
used in such a way that teaches and trains future generations of
Palestinians to hate and seek war, is it really helping them anyway?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel's kid-glove treatment of Gaza]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/19/israels-kid-glove-treatment-of-gaza.html"/>
    <updated>2007-09-19T18:01:30+03:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/19/israels-kid-glove-treatment-of-gaza</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The Palestinians and the international media do their best to convince
the world that Israel is treating the Gaza Strip in a brutal and
oppressive manner. The truth is that Israel&#8217;s leadership is very
stubbornly refusing to take off its kid gloves in dealing with the
mounting threat from Hamas-controlled Gaza, to the continued detriment
of both Israel and the Arabs of Gaza. On Wednesday, the government of
Prime Minister Ehud Olmert made a show of combating the Gaza threat by
<a href="http://www.ynetnews.com/articles/0,7340,L-3451149,00.html">dramatically declaring the volatile coastal strip a “hostile enemy
territory.”</a>
It is a move that will accomplish absolutely nothing. Years ago, as
Yasser Arafat&#8217;s uprising against Israel was getting into full swing, the
government of Ariel Sharon declared the terror icon and his regime
enemies of the Jewish state. The decision gained a lot of international
press coverage, as well as a lot of international scorn, while doing
absolutely nothing to slow down the Palestinian terrorist onslaught. The
moment Arafat was dead the international community fully brushed aside
Israel&#8217;s conclusion that the entire Palestinian regime had become
hostile, and insisted that the time had arrived to rush to a final
status peace agreement. Even less effective will be the limited
sanctions the cabinet also approved on Wednesday. The ministers said
they are ready to cut Israel&#8217;s supply of electricity and fuel to Gaza
(can you believe Israel is still providing these things?), but also
rejected the idea of doing anything that would too adversely affect the
civilian population. Well, cutting electricity and fuel will adversely
affect the civilian population in a very visible way, so you can be sure
the reduction of these basic services will be token in scope. The only
effective solution to the Gaza rocket problem is the one that Olmert&#8217;s
cabinet unanimously rejected - a full ground invasion of Gaza and the
possible reinstating of long-term Israeli control. Security and defense
experts, including some of Olmert&#8217;s own ministers, have been warning for
years that the only way to really curb the threat of rockets from Gaza
is to go in with overwhelming force and crush the local terrorist
infrastructure. Those same experts also warn that any alternative move
that does not eliminate the ability of Hamas and other groups to make
war on Israelis will only encourage the terrorists to continue down
their path of violence. Hamas and their terrorist allies do not need to
actually defeat Israel militarily, just as Hizballah did not need to
actually win the war with Israel last summer. They just had to survive
the war with Israel. That a small terrorist militia went to war with the
mighty Israeli army and survived while inflicting damage on Israeli
civilians was enough to boost Hizballah&#8217;s image among the Arab world
immeasurably. Israel is handing Hamas the same type of victory. Nor does
Hamas care about the suffering of the people living under their control.
In fact, the more the local population suffers from Israeli sanctions
and limited military strikes, the more public relations ammunition Hamas
has. If Israel really cares about putting Hamas out of business and
about ending the suffering of the Arabs of Gaza, it should listen to
those experts who advocate crushing, one-time military action that will
end Hamas&#8217; very ability to function and at the same time end the need
for ongoing Israeli military reprisals that inadvertently harm the
civilian population.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christianity Today's humanist approach to the Israeli-Arab conflict]]></title>
    <link href="http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/16/christianity-todays-humanist-approach-to-the-israeli-arab-conflict.html"/>
    <updated>2007-09-16T19:07:14+03:00</updated>
    <id>http://ryaninzion.github.com/zcom/blog/2007/09/16/christianity-todays-humanist-approach-to-the-israeli-arab-conflict</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The popular Christian magazine _Christianity Today_ recently lent its
support to a letter signed by 34 US Evangelical leaders <a href="http://www.zionist.com/2007/07/30/christian-support-for-palestine-smacks-of-replacement-theology">urging
President George W. Bush to continue down his path of dividing the Land
of
Israel</a>.
The magazine then carried an article <a href="http://www.christianitytoday.com/ct/2007/september/16.24.html">defending its decision to support
that
call</a>.
With all due respect, it appears _Christianity Today_ has, like so
many American churches, allowed secular humanism to creep in and
influence its views on the current conflict. The author of the recent
_Christianity Today_ article says a lot that I can agree with
pertaining to the continued position of the Children of Israel as the
apple of God&#8217;s eye and of the necessity for us as Gentile believers to
realize that we have been grafted into Israel&#8217;s tree of faith. > We
cannot read the New Testament without seeing that the Jews continue to
have a place in God&#8217;s economy. Gentile Christians do not replace the
Jews, but are joint heirs and wild branches grafted onto the Jewish
olive tree. God&#8217;s ultimate purpose in saving Gentile Christians is to
save the Jews (Rom. 11). OK so far, but that is where it starts to break
down for me. The author goes on to suggest that while the Bible may deed
a far greater area of land to Israel than what it today has full
sovereignty over, our Christian obligations toward others forbid us to
support Israel&#8217;s rule over a “Palestinian” population that does not
desire it. > While the most vocal Christian Zionists call for Israel to
possess all of the Davidic “Greater Israel,“ such goals come at too high
a price. The author justifies this position by noting that the majority
of Israelis, even those who do dream of possessing all of the Promised
Land, realize they cannot rule over such a large population of Arabs and
therefore must abandon the hope of a complete fulfillment of God&#8217;s
promises. They must abandon the borders that God Himself drew for Israel
because of the sensitivities and protests of the Muslim world. This is a
very wrong position for a Bible-believer to take. The Israelis who think
this way, even if they are a majority, are failing to fully put their
faith in God and in His promises. We should not be encouraging them to
behave in such a way, and we certainly should not be joining them in
doing so. Fortunately, David Ben Gurion and his contemporaries did not
allow themselves to be influenced by such demographic nonsense and
declared independence despite the Jews being a minority west of the
Jordan River at the time. **Trust in God and in His Word should cause
us to stand firm on His promises even when present circumstances don&#8217;t
appear to be in our favor.** The editors of _Christianity Today_,
while they seem to recognize the continued central importance of Israel
and her restoration in God&#8217;s plans, apparently fail to realize that the
enemy is naturally doing everything in his power to thwart or at least
stall the fulfillment of those plans. That means hindering the
restoration of the land to Israel and of Israel to the land. It is not
wrong to hope and pray for and even try to facilitate a better life for
the Arabs, though their salvation from Islam should be our first
concern. However, by giving succor to the Arab “cause” of dividing and
eventually overrunning the Land of Israel, these Christians are in fact
aiding the schemes of the enemy of our Lord. Another couple of biblical
points I would like to make that contradict the position _Christianity
Today_ has taken are these: 1. The Lord clearly warns against efforts
to divide “My land,” and speaks of severe judgement for those who do
(Joel 3:2). By urging Bush to press on with his “two-state solution,”
these Christians are urging their leader to become one of those the Lord
speaks out against. 2. As Christians, we should recognize that there
will be no peace in the Middle East between Israel and her neighbors
until Messiah returns (Isaiah 2:2, 4) and establishes his rule with an
iron rod (Psalm 2:9). We are called to be peacemakers, but not in a
manner that runs contrary to the rest of God&#8217;s Word and puts us in the
camp of those scorned by the prophets and destined to suffer severe
judgement. That last point speaks to an issue regarding the Church in
America that has bothered me for some time, and that is the fingerprints
of secular humanism that can be seen in so many of the Church&#8217;s views
regarding the Israeli-Arab conflict. God has determined quite clearly
that this land belongs to Him (Leviticus 25:23), and that His intention
is to restore it to Israel (Amos 9:14-15). While God does care about
each of us personally, the fulfillment of our personal desires is far
less important than the fulfillment of His divine will. That the
Palestinian Arabs desire to have their own sovereign nation on this
small piece of land should for us pale in comparison to the expressed
will of God. It is secular humanism that denies Israel its biblical
birthright as a result of Arab whining. Those Arabs refuse to accept the
word, promises and will of God. We should not join them. The
Palestinians&#8217; plight is not rooted in Israel&#8217;s restoration, but rather
in their failure to accept the Lord God of Israel and get in line with
His will. At present, they are pawns of the enemy in his effort to
thwart and hinder God&#8217;s plans. It is wrong for us as Christians to help
keep the Palestinians in this state, when we should be seeking their
salvation from Islam and the clutches of Allah. The position represented
by the editors of _Christianity Today_ and those other Evangelical
leaders who signed that ill-advised letter to Bush is more in line with
politically correct secular humanism than with the Word of God. Also
see: <a href="http://www.olivetreeviews.org/articles/Jans_Articles.shtml#newsitemEElAlVpZkypmGVhTkO">Christianity Today&#8217;s Israel-Bashing: This is Loving
Israel?</a>
by Jan Merkel of Olive Tree Ministries <a href="http://worldnetdaily.com/news/article.asp?ARTICLE_ID=57619">Christianity Today? Or Politics
Today?</a> by
Joseph Farah</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
